But that is what existentialists mean we have to do.
Many existentialists even mean that religion is harmful to individual development
to a free and authentic person who takes responsibility for his or her actions.
The problem with these all -inclusive theories is that they do not take adequate consideration
To what it means to be human.
They assume that meaning and purpose originates from an alternative and objective sphere
such as heaven or Plato's world of ideas.
Many of the traditional religions also answer the philosophical questions
From the perspective of an omniscient God, forwarded to us through prophets.
An existentialist believes that what we need is not a divine perspective, but a human such.
Or as Nietzsche put it, after all, we are "human, too human".